Go ahead, Jesse.
>> Hey, EMTT. Congratulations. Um,
appreciate
>> it. Uh, I've got a couple questions for
you. The first one I wanted to ask about
playing at Arrowhead um, this past year.
What was that experience like? And did
you meet any Chiefs people or players in
that particular game?
>> Yeah, man. It was amazing. Uh, I didn't
get to meet I seen some of the players
walking down the field, but I didn't get
to meet them. But, um, I seen Coach
Reed, too. And, uh, it was just a
blessing to be out there, man. I really
love the field, love the environment,
and I know a lot a lot of Nebraska fans
are going to are going to follow me
there, so it's going to be great.
>> And 161 was a lot later than most mocks
had you going. I just wonder what your
reaction is to that.
>> Uh the same reaction I had my whole
life, man. I've been doubted. I've been
passed on. So, um just just needed
opportunity, honestly. I'm really
blessed for this opportunity. Didn't
matter what pick around. Uh I get to
still put on a football jersey, put on a
football helmet, and uh still go out
there and work. And when it's on the
field, it's not what pick it is. It's
everybody playing football. So, I'm
ready for that.
>> We'll go next to Herby Top. Herby.
>> Hey, Em. Uh, like Jesse said,
congratulations and welcome to Kansas
City. To kind of follow up, Yeah. kind
of follow up what Jesse just asked you
about you probably fallen down there.
>> It seems like, um, you were under
recruited coming out of high school and
you kind of like kept score from the
time you went from high school to your
first carry, 475 days, I believe. How
much of this knowing that people tend to
doubt you kind of fuels you to prove all
the doubters wrong?
>> Man, it fuels me every single second of
the day, man. I uh I just got a chip on
my shoulder. I feel like a box of
Pringles at this point now, but um it
fuels me, man. I've had a lot of things
that, you know, have filled me in the
past. I've been through a lot of
adversity, so I feel like I'm ready for
whatever. And um just needed an
opportunity, like I said, man. I'm going
to be ready to work. And um just can't
wait to get to work. And speaking of
work, the opportunity to work with
Kenneth Walker and even Patrick Mahomes
as a quarterback. How much does that
excite you?
>> I love it, man. I love it because I'm
working with the best of the best, man.
I got, you know, Super Bowl MVP uh
running back and then Pat Mahomes,
somebody who's proven and it's going to
be amazing, man. I love playing against
the best and I love playing with the
best. So, it's going to be fun
opportunity to do that.
>> We'll go next to Sam McDow. Sam.
>> Hey. Um, just can you describe what your
draft day experience was like?
Yeah, it was just a lot of, you know,
having a lot of faith in myself and, you
know, just believing in myself, man. I
know that, um, you know, I didn't go as
early as, you know, people thought I
would go, but I just know that I needed
an opportunity and so I just had faith
the whole time. I know what I am as a
player, so I have no doubt that I'll be
ready, uh, for the NFL and I know I just
needed an opportunity, like I said, and
um, I'm make the most out of it for
sure.
>> Obviously, Nebraska, you played every
down, whether it was rushing or in in
the pass game. What is, uh, just your
involvement in the pass game that you
hope to have in the NFL? Yeah, I'm I'm
going to come in and dominate, man. And
whatever role or whatever, you know,
opportunity I get, I'm going to make the
most out of it. Um, it's going to be
great to come in there, like I said, and
play with the best. And I know that, you
know, I got a good coach and Andy Reid
and just the whole staff in general. I
know they're going to put me in a good
position. But most importantly, I just
know I'm going to come in and work my
butt off and, you know, earn my way like
I've been doing my whole life.
>> We'll go next to Nate Taylor. Nate,
>> well, Emtt, congratulations. I have uh
two questions as well. My first is just
what were the conversations like with
the Chiefs before the draft. How much
conversations did you have? Did you
think they were on your radar?
>> Yeah, I knew uh from the combine, man.
We had a great um great formal interview
at the combine. You know, I feel like
they really loved everything, you know,
about that experience, but I didn't talk
to them much after the combine. Um had a
lot of interest from a lot of schools, a
lot of teams, but I just knew that I
just need one opportunity, man, like I
said, and um whoever chooses me uh is
who I'm going to go all in for. So, they
chose me and then that's all I care
about and I'm just going ready to get to
work.
>> And and we've discussed before about you
being uh maybe uh sort of, you know,
underappreciated throughout your career.
>> If you were to say that you were
considered an overachiever to get to
this point, why would you say you were
able to um maybe beat the odds compared
to what most people thought going into
your college career?
>> Just having self-belief. Like I said in
myself, I know, you know, I know what I
am and I know God had a plan for me. I
know what type of player I am. So, I'm
never worried about what people say. I
just tune on all the noise. And like I
said, my whole life I've been passed on
and doubted. So, I just know that as
long as I got faith in myself and my
abilities, nothing else matters.
>> We'll go next to Nick Jacobs. Nick.
>> Yeah. And Kelsey, I have a followup if I
can, please. EMTT, for you, what does it
mean that you're going to have two
former NFL running backs coaching you?
>> Demarco. Yep.
>> Yeah. What what's it going to mean to
you to have two former NFL running backs
coaching you and DeMarco Murray and Eric
Benemy?
>> Uh it's going to be a blessing, man. I
know, you know, they this is the best of
the best, man. Like I said, Benemy, I
seen a video him told him at the combine
about him talking to AP, man, who I grew
up watching. So, it's just kind of full
circle uh to be have him coaching me,
you know, and I know that he's going to
get the most out of me. He's going to
push me really hard, and that's what I
want uh from a coach.
>> And for you, when you're out there on
the football field, what is it you pride
yourself on that you like to put on tape
for other opponents to see? I pride
myself on dominating all three phases
and that's just running the ball,
catching the ball, and also receive. Oh,
no, run the ball, catching the ball, and
blocking, my bad. And I feel like all
three phases is something I'm going to
come into this NFL and just dominate at
a high level. Uh, I feel like my
versatility is special, and I I don't
think I have a weakness on the football
field, so that's what I'm ready for.
>> It looks like we have two more questions
left and we'll go first to Matt Derek.
Matt,
>> hey EMTT, congratulations. And a couple
of questions for you. you were briefly
in the transfer portal after I think
2024 decided to stick around. What went
into that decision because it certainly
seemed to work out for you.
>> Yes, sir. Uh just a lot of like I said,
faith leaning on leaning on God. Um had
a lot of faith in my offensive
coordinator Dana Hogerson um who was
here and I knew that he was going to put
me in a position to be successful and so
um just let on my faith. You know, I'm
never somebody who wants to leave or
transfer somewhere. I'm always pride
myself on competing with others and just
earning my way. So, um, I didn't really
feel the need to, you know, go somewhere
else and do that. I felt like I had a
lot of trust in Coach Hogerson, uh,
coming back here. Um, and just, like I
said, it worked out the right way. You
know, it was guys playing at the end of
the day.
>> And you were really effective as a pass
catcher as well. What What made you that
way? What did you Was that something you
worked on? Is it something comes natural
to you? What do you like about being
involved in the in the passing game as a
running back?
>> Both, man. Ever since I was 8 years old.
Um, you know, my first coach, coach
Kendrick, put me in a position to not
just be a running threat, but receiving
threat. And I feel like, you know, any
route in the route tree, I'm able to
run. Uh, I study receivers. I don't just
study running backs. I'm not somebody
who just studies running backs. I study
receivers, too. So, I know that I have
the ability to go out there and run
routes in the slot or wherever it may
be. And I can affect the game in
multiple ways. I think it's just it just
brings my value up to a team. So, I know
that if I have a a chance to do that,
you know, at this next level, it'll be
really scary for some defenses.
>> Thanks, EMTT. That's all the questions
that we have for you. We appreciate the
time. Congratulations and welcome to
Kansas City.
>> I appreciate it, Kelsey.
>> Yep. Talk to you soon.
>> Yeah. God bless.